자막제작 - 네이트 드라마 24
(http://club.nate.com/24)
'24' Season 3
Epi 13. 01:00 A.M. - 02:00 A.M.
Epi 13. 01:00 A.M.-02:00 A.M.
FOX 방영일 : 2003년 2월 10일
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON FOX: 2004/02/10
'24' 지난 줄거리
데이비드, 난 여전히
당신의 권위를 믿어요
David, I still believe in your presidency.
만약 알란 밀리켄이 당신의
정치적 권위를 위협한다면
And, if Alan Milliken is threatening
your ability to lead this country,
그는 저지될 거예요
he will be stopped.
밀리켄이 12년 전에
당신 딸을 치여서 죽였죠?
Milliken was driving the car that hit and
killed your daughter 12 years ago?
네, 밀리켄이 그날밤
차를 운전하는 걸 봤어요
Yeah. I saw Milliken
driving the car that night.
켈리가 그걸 본 유일한 사람이에요
Kelly was the only one who saw it.
밀리켄의 부하들이
그를 데려갔어요
Then Milliken's people got to him.
- 그가 증언할 건가?
- 네
He'll swear to this? / Yes.
켈리 씨?
Mr. Kelly?
- 그건 뭐야?
- 아기야
- What is that?
- It's a baby.
그래, 아기지
Yeah, I can see that it's a baby, Kim.
누구 아기야?
Whose baby is it?
- 클로이
- 클로이는 아기가 없어
- Chloe's.
- Chloe doesn't have a baby.
아담이 방금 당신이 이 아이의
엄마가 아니라고 했어요
Adam just told me you're not
the mother of this child.
솔직히 그녀는 망상에
빠진 거 같아요
Frankly, I think she's delusional.
이곳에서 체이스가 보내는 오디오를
필터링 할 수 있는 건 그녀뿐이야
She's the only one in this office
capable of filtering audio streams
that chase is sending us.
만약 클로이가 불안정하면..
If Chloe is unstable...
우린 지금 대안이 없어
We don't have an alternative right now.
그녀를 계속 일하게 해야 돼
We have got to keep her in place.
아마도어가 여기에
15분 후에 올 거야
Amador will be here in 15 minutes.
바이러스인지 확인하면
Confirm that he has the virus,
그한테 돈을 주고 바이러스는
우리한테 가지고 와
give him his money, and
bring the virus back to us.
잘했어
Good job.
넌 더 이상 필요 없어
I don't need you anymore.
그를 죽일 거예요
델타 부대는 제때에 못 와요
He's going to kill him.
Delta team's not going to get there in time.
라몬, 우린 약속을 했어
Ramon, we had a deal.
- 체이스!
- 토니, 델타 부대가 왔어요
- Chase!
- Tony, delta's here.
우리가 원하는 건 바이러스야
All we want is the virus.
실린더를 천천히 내려놔
Just put the cylinder down slowly.
엎드려!
Get down!
우리한테 바이러스가 없다!
We do not have the virus!
라몬이 가졌던 실린더는 폭탄이었어
The cylinder Ramon was carrying
was rigged with a bomb.
아마도어가 바꾼 게 틀림없어
그의 위치를 알아?
Amador must have switched it.
Do we have a position on him?
델타 부대가 쫓고 있어요, 잭
Delta has a team on him, Jack.
멀리 가지 못할 거예요
He won't get far.
손 위로 올려!
Hands in the air!
바닥에 엎드려라
Get on the ground.
잭, 아마도어가 델타 3팀을
매복 공격했어요
Jack, Amador ambushed Delta 3.
- 함정이었어요
- 그의 위치는?
- It was a setup.
- What about his position?
매복 공격이 일어나고
신호를 놓쳤어요
We lost the signal once
the ambush happened.
개자식
Son of a bitch.
델타 3팀이 제거됐어
Delta 3's been taken out.
아마도어의 위치를 몰라
They don't have a position on Amador.
- 어떻게 할까요?
- 니나를 찾아야 돼
- What do you want to do?
- We've got to find Nina.
이 이야기는 오전 1시부터
2시 사이에 일어난 일입니다
The Following Takes Place
Between 1:00 a.m. And 2:00 a.m.
영어대본
김혜정(heather81@nate.com)
자막편집/싱크
남효주(hyojunet@nate.com)
한글번역
플라스틱(http://club.nate.com/24)
제작지원
박창희(jfpark@nate.com)
- 잭?
- 바우어다
Jack? / This is Bauer.
소방도로를 지나 불빛이 보여요
당신인가요?
I have an area lit up past
the fire road. Is that you?
아니야
Negative.
- 확인해 볼게요
- 조심해
- I'll check it out.
- Be careful.
거기 멈춰
Stop right there.
총을 버려
Drop your gun.
어서!
Drop it!
머리에 손 올려
Get your hands on your head.
잭하고 무전하고 있지?
You on a two-way with Jack?
그래
Yeah.
그에게 코드 6을 줘
Give him a code six.
가방에서 무전기를 꺼낼게
I'm going to reach in my bag,
and I'm going to pull out a two-way.
천천히..
Slowly.
잭?
Jack?
그래
Yeah?
코드 6이에요
I'm code six.
네가 봤던 빛은 뭐야?
What about the light you saw?
아무것도 아니에요
It was nothing.
끊어, 대기로 하지 말고
Off. Not standby.
여기로 던져
Throw it over here.
누가 또 이 지역에 있지?
Who else is on the grid with you?
- 나하고 잭뿐이야
- 거짓말 하지 마
- Just me and Jack.
- You're lying.
델타 부대를 봤어
I saw a delta team.
- 그들은 북쪽으로 갔어
- 아마도어는?
- They went north.
- What about Amador?
바이러스를 가지고 도망쳤어
He escaped with the virus.
그는 모두를 속인 거야
He ripped off everybody.
개자식
Son of a bitch.
좋아
All right.
언덕 아래로 움직여
Move down the hill.
- 어디로 가지?
- 그냥 걸어
- Where we going?
- Just walk.
괜찮나?
You okay?
네
Yeah.
델타에 연락해서
Contact delta.
비행장에서 만나자고 해
Tell them to meet us at the airfield.
그녀를 어떻게 할 거죠, 잭?
What are you going
to do to her, Jack?
- 심문할 거야
- 아니야, 안 할 거야
- Interrogate her.
- No, he's not.
닥쳐!
Shut up!
체이스, 제발..
Chase, please.
그냥 날 믿어
Just trust me.
비행장에서 만날게요
I'll meet you at the airfield.
잭, 아마도어가 아직
바이러스를 가졌어
Jack, Amador still has the virus.
그를 쫓도록 도와줄 수 있어
I can help you track him.
그가 이 마을을 고른 이유는
국경하고 가깝기 때문이야
The only reason he chose this town
is because it's close to the border.
그는 LA로 돌아가야 하거든
He needs to get back to Los Angeles.
일단 돌아가면 누군가를 만나서
Once he does, he's
going to meet somebody,
바이러스를 주고 사라질 거야
unload the virus, and disappear.
그를 찾는 걸 도와줄 수 있어
I can help you find him.
잭, 난 죽고 싶지 않아
Jack, I don't want to die.
그를 찾는 걸 돕게 해줘
Let me help you find him.
당신을 도와줄 수 있어
I can help you.
- CTU입니다
- 여긴 잭 바우어
CTU. / This is Jack Bauer.
알메이다를 연결해 줘요
Patch me through to Almeida.
알메이다입니다
Almeida.
니나 마이어스를 생포했어
I've got Nina Myers alive.
아마도어의 흔적은?
Any sign of Amador?
델타 부대를 공격한 후에는 없어요
No. Not since he ambushed
the delta team.
위성이 돌아오면 훑어 볼 거예요
Once the satellite comes around,
we'll do a sweep.
그가 LA로 향하고 있다고 니나가 말했어
Nina says he's headed to Los Angeles.
그녀를 믿나요?
You believe her?
뭔가를 아는 것 같아
그녀는 협상을 원해
I think she knows something.
She wants to cut a deal.
CTU로 데리고 갈게
We got to bring her back to CTU.
좋아요, 델타 비행기를 준비해 둘게요
Okay. I'll get a delta plane ready.
알았어
Copy that.
일어나, 천천히..
Get up... slowly.
토니, 내가 너무 많은 통신을
조절하고 있어요
Tony, I'm coordinating
too many comms.
아담 그룹에 좀 나눠 줘야겠어요
I need to offload some
of it to Adam's group.
모두 받았어?
You have everything?
그래
Yeah.
이봐, 클로이
Look, Chloe,
샤펠한테 가서 얘기해 봐
you need to go talk to Chappelle.
뭘 말이에요?
For what?
무슨 말인지 알잖아
You know what for.
- 킴 바우어입니다
- 기록들 다 갱신했어?
Kim Bauer. / Did you get a
chance to update the logs?
대부분이요. 아빠하고
체이스는 어떻게 됐어요?
Most of them. Look, what's
going on with my dad and Chase?
그게 내가 전화한 이유야
That's why I called.
그들은 LA로 돌아오고 있어
They're headed back to Los Angeles.
아마도어를 놓쳐서
우리가 지금 찾고 있어
They lost Amador.
We're looking for him now.
니나는요?
What about Nina?
그들이 데려오고 있어
They're bringing her back with them.
고마워요, 토니
Thank you, Tony.
좋아, 천만에
Right. You got it.
좋지만 우선순위를 정해야 돼
I'd love nothing more, but
we have to prioritize, don't we?
알겠습니다
I understand.
좋아. 그래
All right.
이만 끊어야겠어
Yeah. All right. I got to go.
저하고 얘기하고 싶다고
했다면서요? 여기 왔어요
Tony said you wanted
to talk to me. Here I am.
- 앉아
- 아기 얘기로 부른 거면 시간 낭비예요
Sit down. / If you want me to talk about
the baby, you're wasting your time
그애에 대해 얘기하지 않을 거예요
because I'm not going to talk about her.
그래서 앉으라는 거야
So, sit down.
무슨 일인지 말해줘
Tell me what the hell is going on.
뭘요?
What?
좋아
All right.
처음에 그 아기가
자네 아이라고 했지
First, you told us
the baby was yours.
그게 거짓말인 걸 알게 됐어
We found out that was a lie.
그러자 그 아기가 학대를 받아서
Then you tell us
you and your boyfriend
자네와 자네 남자친구가
데려왔다고 했지
took it from its mother because
the baby was being abused.
그렇게 말했었는데
지금 바꾸고 싶어요
I did say that, and I'd like
to correct that right now.
전 남자친구가 없어요
I don't have a boyfriend.
믿을 수가 없군
You're unbelievable.
그럼 누구 아기야?
Who does the baby belong to?
말해줄 수 없어요
I can't tell you.
자넨 이 건물에 허가받지 않은
사람을 데리고 들어왔어
You brought an unauthorized
person into this building.
그건 연방법 위반이야
That's a federal offense.
- 그냥 아기일 뿐이에요
- 그게 누구든 상관없어
- It's just a baby.
- I don't care who it is.
규정을 위반했어
You're in violation.
좋아요. 위반했어요
Fine. I'm in violation.
누구 아기지, 클로이?
Who does the
baby belong to, Chloe?
실험실에서 혈액검사를 해서
신원확인을 하기 바라는 거야?
Do you want me to
take it down to the lab
and run blood tests to get an I.D.?
- 난 그렇게 할 거야
- 아기에 대해선 더 이상 말하지 않겠어요
Because I will. / I'm not going to
talk any more about this baby.
그건 내가 무섭고 사악한
사람이기 때문이 아니에요
And it's not because
I'm a horrible, evil person.
그냥 그럴 수 없어요
It's just because I can't do it.
제발 그애에게
주사 바늘을 꽂지 마세요
Just please don't start
sticking needles in her.
- 아일린?
- 네, 샤펠 씨
- Eileen?
- Yes, Mr. Chappelle.
경비를 들여보내
Send security in.
아기에게 몇 가지 실험을 할 동안
클로이 오브라이언을 지키도록 해
I want Chloe O'Brian under guard
while we run some tests on the baby.
바로 보낼게요
Right away, sir.
CTU의 토니 알메이다가 멕시코에서
Tony Almeida from CTU
has just informed us
코딜라 바이러스를 압수하지
못했다고 알려 왔어요
that they were unable to confiscate
this Cordilla virus in Mexico.
판매자의 위치를 파악하고
그 구역 전체를 포위한 줄 알았는데
I thought they located the seller and
had the entire area surrounded.
마이클 아마도어라는 이 판매자는
Well, this seller-- a man
named Michael Amador--
바이러스를 줄 생각이
없었던 게 분명해요
apparently, he never intended
to give up the virus.
잘 계획된 속임수였어요
In fact, it was a well-planned rip-off
데이비드, 우린 여섯 명을 잃었어요
David, we lost six men.
델타 부대 소속이에요
Members of a delta team.
델타 부대 하나를 잃었군
We lost a delta team.
아마도어는 지금 어디 있어?
This man Amador--
where is he now?
가장 최근의 가설은
아마도어가 바이러스를 가지고
Latest working theory is that
Amador has this virus, and is
여기 LA로 돌아오고 있다는 거예요
headed back here to Los Angeles.
살포하기 위해서?
To release it?
몰라요. 하지만 아마도어가 테러
공격을 일으켰던 과거는 없어요
We don't know, but Amador doesn't have
a history of implementing terrorist strikes.
그는 사상을 알 수 없는 무기상이에요
He's an arms dealer
with no known ideology.
결론은 우린 아직 그의 의도가
뭔지 모른다는 거죠
Bottom line is we just don't
know what his intentions are.
방해해서 죄송합니다, 각하
Sorry to interrupt, sir.
셰리 팔머에게 연락이 닿았습니다
I finally reached Sherry Palmer.
지금 연결되어 있나?
Is she on the line now?
네, 각하
Yes, sir.
계속 진행하게, 웨인
Continue here, Wayne.
- 셰리
- 데이비드, 다시 전화 못해서 미안해요
Sherry. / David, I'm sorry
I couldn't call you back.
켈리의 집을 서둘러 떠나야 했어요
I had to leave Kelly's in a hurry.
나와 얘기하고 나서
그하고 다시 얘기해 봤어?
Did you go back and
talk to him after we spoke?
그게 다예요. 다시 돌아갔더니
그가 사라졌어요
That's just it. When I got
back there, he was gone.
사라져?
Gone?
그가 달아났다고 생각해?
You think he ran?
아니요. 그는 기꺼이 밀리켄에
맞설 준비가 되어 있었어요
No, I don't,
because he was more than ready and
willing to come forward against Milliken.
하지만 누군가 먼저
그를 잡은 게 분명해요
But someone obviously got to him first.
당신은 아무도 못 봤어?
But you didn't see anyone?
네, 차로 급히 돌아와서
거길 빠져나왔어요
No. I ran back to my car
and got out of there.
난 어..
I was, uh...
무서웠어요, 데이비드
I was pretty scared there, David.
밀리켄이 당신을 쫓는 게 틀림없어
Milliken must be on to you.
최대한 빨리 여기로 돌아와
Get back here as soon as you can.
밖에 있는 건 더 이상
안전하지 않아
It's not safe for you out there anymore.
먼저 해야 할 일이 있어요
I really need to do something first.
뭐?
What?
줄리아 밀리켄을 만나러 갈 거예요
I've gotta go see Julia Milliken.
아니, 아니야. 오늘밤엔 그녀나
알란 근처에 가지 말도록 해
No, no. I don't want you to go
anywhere near her or Alan tonight.
그래야 해요, 데이비드
I have to, David.
알란 밀리켄이 케빈 켈리를
납치하거나..
Alan Milliken had to move fast
in order to kidnap--
어쩌면 죽이기 위해
급히 움직였을 거예요
maybe even kill this Kevin Kelly guy.
그가 흔적을 지우기 전에
그걸 이용해야 돼요
I've got to take advantage of that
before he has time to cover his tracks.
셰리, 당신이 알란과
만나는 걸 원치 않아
Sherry,
I do not want you confronting Alan.
말했잖아요, 데이비드
I told you, David,
줄리아하고만 얘기할 거예요
I'm just going to talk to Julia.
알란을 멀리하겠다고 약속할게요
I promise, I'll stay away from Alan.
- 셰리..
- 데이비드
Sherry... / David,
나한테 도움을 요청했죠?
you asked me
to help you, right?
제발 당신을 돕게 놔두세요
Please,
let me do that.
거기서 무슨 일이 있었어요?
What happened back there?
우리가 아마도어를 찾는 걸
도와주겠다는군
She wants to help us find Amador.
바우어 요원, 델타 4팀의
마이크 머피입니다
Agent Bauer, Mike Murphy, Delta 4.
해군에서 C-130기의
항로를 조정했습니다
The navy was good enough
to reroute a C-130.
우리가 고마워한다고 전해줘요
Tell them we said thank you.
우린 당신들과 죄수를
LA로 데리고 갈 겁니다
We're going to take you and
the prisoner back to Los Angeles.
아마도어의 움직임은요?
Any movement on Amador?
없어요. 공중 전술팀이
전 구역을 감시하고 있지만
No. Air tactical's been
monitoring the entire area.
아직까지는 없어요
So far, nothing.
잭, 정말 떠나고 싶어요?
Jack, you sure you want to leave?
이 여자를 결박하게
Secure her.
네
Yes, sir.
아마도어는 이미 사라졌어
Amador's already gone.
아주 치밀하게 계획한 거야
He's planned this thing well.
누가 바이러스를 원하고
We need to find who wants the virus,
언제 어디서 그걸
살포하려는지 알아내려면
and where and when
they're going to release it.
지금 가야 돼
떠납시다
We need to go now.
We need to leave.
- 여보세요
- 마커스, 나야
Hello. / Marcus, it's me.
어디 있어?
Where are you?
거기 1시간 후에 갈 거야
I'll be there in an hour.
바이러스는 갖고 있어?
Got the virus?
그래
Yes.
준비나 해
Just be ready.
그럴게
I will be.
여보세요
Hello?
줄리아, 거의 다 왔어
Julia, I'm almost there.
알란은 지금 어디 있지?
Where is Alan now?
- 방에 있어요
- 자고 있어?
- He's in his room.
- Is he asleep?
아니요, 방금 누군가와
통화를 끝냈어요
No. He just got off the
phone with someone.
누구하고 얘기한 줄 알아?
Do you know who he was talking to?
- 이름 들었어?
- 아니요
- Did you hear a name?
- No. No.
그가 모르게 어떻게 들어갈 수 있지?
How do I get to you
without him knowing?
대문의 암호가 4132예요
The gate code is 4132.
길가에 주차하고
주방 옆문으로 오세요
Park off to the side, then
walk up to the service porch.
- 거기 있을게요
- 좋아, 번호가 뭐라고 했지?
- I'll be there.
- All right,
what's that number again?
4132.
좋아, 감시 카메라가 있나?
Okay. Are there any
security cameras?
네
Yes.
작동하지 못하도록 해
Then make sure they're disabled.
셰리, 내가 할 수 있을지 모르겠어요
Sherry, I don't know if I can.
방법을 찾아봐, 줄리아
Find a way, Julia.
곧 거기 도착할 거야
I'll be there in a few minutes.
...여론조사에서 앞서고
미국민들의 지지를 받고 있습니다
...is ahead in the polls
and gaining favor
with the American people.
팔머 대통령은...
As for President Palmer...
늦게까지 안 자는군요
You're up late.
켄이 싱가포르에서 전화했어
Ken called from Singapore.
아직도 시차 계산하는 걸 못하고 있어
He still hasn't figured out how to
calculate the time difference.
당신도 자야지
You should be in bed yourself.
그럴 거예요
I will.
방금 차를 끓였어요
I just put on some tea.
속을 진정시키려고요
I'd like to settle my stomach.
좋아, 그럼
All right, then.
좋아요
All right.
잘 자요
Good night.
잘 자
줄리아
Julia.
전에 기분이 안 좋았다는 거 알아
I know you felt demeaned earlier,
하지만 그건 이제 과거 일이야
but that's behind us now.
나도 알아요
I know it is.
널 살게 해줬으니 아는 대로 말해
I let you live,
tell me what you know.
아마도어가 서부 해안에서
사업을 할 때면
Anytime Amador does business
on the west coast,
알버스란 사람을 통해서 거래를 했어
he washes his deal through
a man named Alvers.
알버스?
Alvers?
이름은 뭐지?
What's his first name?
내가 아는 건 알버스뿐이야
그건 이름일 수도 성일 수도 있어
All I know is Alvers.
It could be a first or a last name.
아마도어가 어떻게
알버스하고 연락을 하지?
How does Amador contact this Alvers?
몰라
그를 만난 적은 없어
I don't know.
I've never met him.
하지만 이 거래 전에
아마도어 뒷조사를 할 때
But I did check out Amador
before our deal,
알버스란 이름이 계속 나왔었어
and I kept coming
across the name Alvers.
과거의 많은 거래들이
그와 연결되고
He was a connector to
a lot of his past deals, and
LA가 언제나 중심이었더군
Los Angeles was always the hub.
체이스, CTU하고 통화 중이야?
Chase, you on with CTU?
네, 토니예요
Yeah. It's Tony.
그하고 얘기하고 싶다고 전해
Tell him I want to speak to him.
토니, 잭이 얘기하고 싶대요
Tony, Jack wants to talk to you.
- 토니
- 잭
- Tony.
- Hey, Jack.
알버스란 이름을 확인해줘
I want you to run a check
on the name Alvers.
마이클 아마도어에 대한
모든 자료와 교차 확인을 해봐
Cross-reference it with everything
you've got on Michael Amador.
그게 다예요?
Is that it?
그래, 그냥 이름뿐이야
- Yeah.
- Just the name--
알버스, A-l-v-e-r-s
Alvers. A-l-v-e-r-s.
니나한테 이걸 얻었나요?
You got this from Nina?
그래
Yeah.
좋아요, 알아보고
다시 연락할게요
All right, I'll work it up,
I'll get back to you.
좋아, 고마워
Okay, thanks.
가지고 있어요
Keep it.
- 손은 어때?
- 걱정하지 말아요, 괜찮아요
- How's the hand?
- Don't worry about it, it's fine.
체이스, 너하고 난
오늘 많은 일을 겪었어
Look, Chase, you and I have
been through a lot today.
그건 잊도록 하고
지금 맡은 일을 하자
Why don't we try and move
past it and do our job.
당신은 날 믿지 않아요, 잭
You don't trust me, Jack.
헥터하고의 거래를
왜 얘기하지 않았어요?
Why didn't you tell me
about your deal with Hector?
그건 게일, 토니, 그리고
나만 알아야 했어
It couldn't go beyond
Gael, Tony and myself.
그래야만 비밀을 지킬 수 있었어
That's the only way
I knew I could contain it.
그럼 내가 라몬하고 당신을
쫓아가지 않을 거라고 생각했나요?
And what did you think, that I wasn't
going to come after you and Ramon?
난 당신을 구해야 할지
죽여야 할지 몰랐어요
I didn't know whether
to save you or kill you.
난 네가 내 명령을 따르길 바랐어
I expected you to follow my orders.
하지만 아마 나도 똑같이 했을 거야
But I probably would have
done the same thing myself.
당신은 내 머리에 총을 대고..
You put a gun to my head...
방아쇠를 당겼어요
and you pulled the trigger.
난 라몬 살라자르가
날 테스트하기 위해서
I made a judgment call that
Ramon Salazar would not
장전된 무기를 주지는
않을 거라고 판단했어
give me a loaded weapon--
that he was testing me.
만약 장전됐었다면?
And if it was loaded?
그럼 뭐죠?
Then what?
내 임무를 마쳤을 거야
I'd have finished my mission.
체이스, 내 말 들어
Chase, listen to me.
이 일을 오래 하다 보면
선택을 해야 될 때가 있을 거야
You do this job long enough,
you're going to have to make choices,
그리고 전체 시나리오가 끝날 때까지는
자신이 옳은 선택을 했는지 알 수가 없지
and you don't know
you've made the right one
until the whole scenario plays itself out.
지금 당장 문제가 되는 건
우리가 이 바이러스를 멈추지 못하면
Right now the only thing that matters
is if we don't stop this virus,
우리가 아는 세상은
영원히 바뀔 거라는 거야
the world as we know it
will change forever.
그리고 너도 알다시피
그 사실 하나만을 염두에 둬야 해
And that fact, and that fact alone
is the only thing that you have to keep
in the front of your mind, and you know that.
그래요
Yeah.
그래
왜 계속 그녀를 압박하지 않죠?
Why don't you keep pressing her?
아마 모든 걸 말하지 않았을 거예요
She probably hasn't
told you everything.
그래, 아마 그랬겠지
No, she probably hasn't.
우린 기다려야 해
We're going to have to wait.
알버스가 진짜 단서인지 확인해야 돼
Make sure Alvers is a real lead.
CIA 데이터베이스에서
수천 명의 알버스가 나왔어요
Over a thousand Alvers showed up
in the Langley database.
배경 확인을 하고
아마도어와 맞춰 보니
I did background checks and
consistency-refs with Amador.
이게 조건에 들어맞는
유일한 사람이에요
This is the only one that red flagged.
마커스 알버스
Marcus Alvers.
오스트리아에서 태어나서
영국으로 갔어요
Born in Austria, moved to England.
캠브리지에서 생물학을 공부하면서
아마도어를 만났어요
Met Amador in Cambridge where
Alvers was studying biology.
1994년에 그들이 무기화된 탄저균을
만들었다는 혐의가 있었지만
In 1994, they were suspected of
manufacturing weapons-grade anthrax,
물증이 없었어요
but there was no hard evidence.
이게 우리가 찾던 놈인 것 같군
Sounds like this is our guy.
서류상으로 알버스와 아마도어는 분명히
지난 몇 년 동안 행적이 일치해요
Yeah, the dossier's sketchy,
but Alvers and Amador have definitely
crossed paths over the years.
CIA 서류에 이게 있었어요
CIA had these on file.
지난 3년 동안 알버스와 아마도어가
유럽과 동아프리카에서
Over the past three years, there have been
14 sightings of Alvers and Amador together
함께 있는 게 14번 목격됐어요
throughout Europe and east Africa.
좋아, 그럼 알버스를 어떻게 찾지?
All right, so how do we find Alvers?
단서가 몇 개 있어요
모두 조사해 봐야 하죠
We have some threads.
We need to work them all up.
본부에서 사람이 더 필요해요
We're going to need
manpower from Division.
미셸, 더 불러와
Michelle, hook them up.
- 바우어입니다
- 잭, 알버스를 확인했어요
Bauer. / Yeah, Jack, we got
a match on Alvers.
지금 그를 찾으려 하는데
시간이 걸릴 거예요
Now we got to find him.
It's going to take some time.
좋아, 여기서 할 수 있는 일을 알아볼게
Okay, I'll see what we
can do from here.
맞았어
We're on.
알버스에 대해 네가 준
정보는 진짜였어
Looks like the information
you gave us on Alvers is real.
물론이지
Of course it is.
CTU는 그가 아마도어와
만나기 전에 찾지 못할 거야
CTU is not going to find him
before his meeting with Amador.
하지만 내가 도와줄 수 있어
But I can help you.
어떻게?
How?
아까 내가 말했던 것보다
더 많이 알고 있어
I know a little more
than I said I did.
사면서를 받을 시간이 없는 걸 아니까
Look, I know there's no
time for a signed deal,
내가 바이러스를 확보하도록 돕는다면
so I'm going to trust you to support
my case with the Department of Justice
당신이 법무부에 잘 말해
줄 거라고 믿을게
if I help you secure this virus.
약속하지
You've got my word.
그 남자의 이름은
마커스 프레드릭 알버스야
The man's name is
Marcus Fredrick Alvers.
그는 아마추어 생물학자이고
테러리스트가 되고 싶어해
He's an amateur biologist
and wanna-be terrorist.
비엔나와 LA에서 물의를 일으켰고
중간에 2년간 런던에서 머물렀지
Raised hell from Vienna to Los Angeles,
with a two-year stop in London.
나한테 그의 번호가 있어
I have a number for him.
먼저 펠코 시내국번으로 걸면
You have to dial a Felco prefix first,
인터넷을 통해 그한테 연결돼
and then you can reach him
through an internet socket.
보안 전화를 줘
Give me the cold line.
번호가 뭐지?
What's the number?
1-7-7-5-5-3-1
1-7-7
5-5-3-1.
빠른 통화중 신호가
나와도 끊지 마
You're going to get a fast
busy signal, but don't hang up.
통화중 신호가 나와
I've got the busy signal.
9번을 3초 동안 누르고 있어
Hit nine and hold it
for three seconds.
신호가 떨어졌어?
Do you get a tone?
그래, 신호가 떨어졌어
Yeah, I've got a tone.
9-5-7-3-1-*-6을 눌러
Hit 95731*6.
신호가 가고 있어
It's ringing.
신호가 멈추면
일련의 번호를 받을 거야
When the ringing stops, you're
going to get a series of numbers--
그게 당신의 IP 주소야
that's your IP address.
신호가 멈췄어
It stopped ringing.
아무 번호도 안 나와
I'm not getting any numbers.
괜찮아
그냥 기다려
That's okay.
Just wait.
도대체 이게 뭐야?
- 네
- 전산실이 난리예요
Yeah? / The tech room is
spiking all over the place.
거기서 리셋할 수 있나요?
Can you reset it from there?
몰라. 다시 전화할게
I don't know.
I'll have to get back to you.
아담, 무슨 일이야?
내 시스템이 잠겼어
Adam, what's going on?
My system's locked.
본부 전산실입니다
Division. Tech.
- 매트, CTU의 아담이에요
- 그래, 아담
- Matt, it's Adam at CTU.
- Yeah, Adam, look.
무슨 일인지 모르겠어
여기도 차단되었어
We don't know what's going on.
Our cable's blocked up here.
다시 연락할게
I'll get back to you.
다시 전화할 필요 없어, 잭
한 번이면 충분해
Don't need to dial it again, Jack.
Once was enough.
무슨 말을 하는 거야?
What are you talking about?
당신은 방금 기관 간의 연결을
끊는 웜을 작동시켰어
You just triggered a worm that's going
to bring down agency connectivity.
세상에.. 뭘 한 거야?
My god, what have you done?
무슨 짓을 한 거냐고!
What have you done?!
내가 말하지 않는 한, 대 테러
컴퓨터 네트워크 전체는 막혔어
Until I say otherwise, your entire
anti-terrorist computer network is jammed.
잘 들어!
Listen up!
시스템에 침입한
자기 번식 코드가 있다!
We got some kind self-propagating
code leaking into the system!
소켓들을 차단하고
할 수 있는 건 모두 저장해!
Shut down your sockets,
save everything you can!
어디서 이게 왔는지 찾아내야 돼
We got to find where
this thing came from.
니나가 이걸 했다는 게
무슨 뜻이에요?
What do you mean, Nina did this?
그녀는 거기서 일할 때 누구보다
시스템에 대해서 잘 알았어
She knew our system better than
anyone when she worked there.
우리가 결코 업데이트 하지 않을
드라이버에 웜을 심어 둔 거야
She embedded a worm
into a part of the driver
that she knew we'd never upgrade.
- 그녀가 그렇게 말했어요?
- 그래
She told you this? / Yes.
원하는 게 뭐래요?
What does she want?
몰라, 곧 알아낼 거야
I don't know.
We're gonna find out soon enough.
우리쪽 사람들이 이걸 막을 수 있을까?
Look, can your people stop this thing?
최선을 다하고 있어요, 잭
We're doing our best, Jack.
내 부서의 클로이를 불러
Pull Chloe out of my sector.
그녀가 누구보다 네트워크를 잘 알아
She knows the network
better than anyone.
그건 문제가 되겠군요
It's going to be a problem.
- 물러나도록 명령받았거든요
- 무슨 말을 하는 거야? 왜?
- She's been asked to step aside.
- What are you talking about? Why?
이야기가 길어요, 잭
It's a long story, Jack.
토니, 지금은 클로이를
일에서 제외시킬 때가 아니야
Tony, this is not the time
to take Chloe out of play.
매일 얼마나 많은 테러 조직들이
우리 시스템을 해킹하려는지 잘 알잖아
You know as well as I do
how many terrorist cells try to
hack into our system every day.
이게 우리 방화벽을 파괴해서
This thing eats through our firewalls,
아침이면 우리 요원들이
목표가 될 거야
we're gonna have
agents as targets by morning.
알았어요. 니나는 어때요?
All right. What about Nina?
이걸 막는 방법을 그녀가
말하도록 할 방도는 없나요?
Is there any way you can get her to
tell us how to neutralize this thing?
시도해 보려고 해
다시 연락하지
I'll start working on it.
I'll get back to you.
알았어요
All right.
원하는 게 뭐야?
What do you want?
비행기를 돌려서 멕시코로 돌아가
Turn the plane around and
head back to Mexico.
그렇게 하면 웜이 퍼지는 걸 늦춰 주지
Once you do, I'll slow down
the spread of the worm.
착륙해서 내가 안전하게 멀리 가면
마지막 제거 암호를 줄게
When we land and I'm safely away,
I'll give you the final kill code.
그런 일은 없을 거야
That will never happen.
얼마나 많은 테러 조직들이
이런 기회를 기다리고 있을까?
How many terrorist cells are
waiting for a window like this?
2백 개?
A couple hundred?
30분이면 사방에서 CTU 파일에
접근할 수 있을 거야
In 30 minutes, they'll all have
access to CTU files everywhere.
그런 일이 일어나길 바라진 않겠지
You don't want that to happen.
비행기를 돌려
Turn the plane around.
우리 사람들이 이걸 막지
못할 거라고 추측하는군
You're assuming our people
can't stop this thing.
한번 노력해 봐
I invite you to try.
날 믿어요, 라이언
알고 있어요
Believe me, Ryan, I know.
지금 당장은 클로이가 웜을 막기 위한
코드를 잘 알고 있는 유일한 사람이에요
Right now, Chloe's the only person
who knows enough about this section
of code to stop the worm.
좋아
Fine.
스티브, 가도 좋네
Steve, you can go.
네
Yes, sir.
무슨 일이에요?
What's happening?
우리 네트워크를
파괴하고 있는 웜이 있어
There's a worm eating
through our network.
니나 마이어스가 원격으로
어떻게 작동을 시켜서
Nina Myers somehow managed
to launch it remotely, and
지금 커널에서 날뛰고 있어
it's running rampant in the kernel.
토니 말이 자네가 막을 수
있다고 하더군. 사실인가?
Tony says you can stop it.
Is that correct?
네, 라우팅 자료를 너무 많이
파괴하지 않았다면요
Yeah, if it hasn't destroyed
too much of the routing data.
좋아, 어서 해
Good. Do it.
아담, 모든 게이트웨이를 닫았어?
Adam, did you close all the gateways?
- 그래
- 12번하고 14번을 다시 열어
Yeah. / Reopen 12 and 14.
뭐하게?
What for? / They won't leak into the rest of
the system, and they get us to the kernel.
나머지 시스템으로는 침입하지 않고
커널로 들어갈 수 있어
달튼, 전산실 노드에
핑을 보내기 시작해
Dalton, start pinging
the nodes in the I.T.
패킷 손실이 없어지면 연산을 멈춰
When you stop getting packet loss,
freeze the process.
- 난 전살실에 가 있을게
- 알았어
I'll be in the tech room. / All right.
당신이 여기 있는 게 불편해요, 셰리
I'm really not comfortable
with you being here, Sherry.
그냥 원하는 게 뭔지 말하지 그래요?
So why don't you just
tell me what you want?
오, 이런.. 줄리아
Oh, come on, Julia.
전에 말했잖아
I told you earlier.
당신 결혼에 대해 안다고..
I know about your marriage.
당신 삶에 대해 알고 있어
I know about your life.
사랑하는 사람과 함께 있고 싶지만
I know that you'd rather be
with the man that you love,
알란의 돈과 안전 때문에
같이 산다는 걸 알아
but you stay with Alan because of
his money and the security.
약식 정신과 상담은 필요 없어요
I don't need a drive-through shrink,
여기 온 특별한 이유가 없다면..
so unless you have some
real reason to be here...
살인은 어때?
How about murder?
무슨 말을 하는 거예요?
What are you talking about?
케빈 켈리라는 남자가
A man named Kevin Kelly
알란에게 큰 타격을 줄
정보를 가지고 있는데
has information on Alan
that could hurt him very badly.
한 시간 전에
An hour ago,
켈리가 사라졌어
Kelly disappeared.
- 사라졌다고요?
- 그가 살해당했을 가능성이 있어
- Disappeared?
- It's possible he was killed.
- 알란이 관련되었다고 생각하나요?
- 오, 알란이 관련된 걸 알아
- And you think Alan is involved?
- Oh, sweetie, I know Alan is involved.
그리고 당신이 그걸
증명하도록 도와줄 거야
And you're going to help me prove it.
내가 도울 수 있다 하더라도
Even if I could do that,
- 왜 그렇게 해야 하죠?
- 당신이 여길 빠져나갈 기회이기 때문이야
- why would I?
- Because it's your ticket out of here.
알란이 감옥에 간다면
If Alan goes to prison,
당신이 모든 걸 갖는 거야, 줄리아
you get everything, Julia.
내가 뭘 하기를 바라는 거죠?
What would you need me to do?
좋아, 먼저
Okay, first,
지난 2시간 동안, 그가 누구와
통화했는지 알아내야 돼
I need you to find out what phone
calls he's made in the past two hours.
알란은 모든 통화를 문을 닫고 해요
Alan makes all his phone calls
behind closed doors.
- 집 전화를 사용하나?
- 핸드폰요
- Does he use the house phone?
- His cell.
대개 가지고 다녀요
휠체어 때문에 그게 휠씬 편하죠
He usually keeps it with him. It makes
things a lot easier with his wheelchair.
핸드폰은 지금 어디 있지?
Where's the cell phone now?
그의 방에요
In his room.
그 전화기를 가져다줘
I need you to get that phone.
안 돼요. 알란은 방금 누웠어요
No. Alan just went to bed.
잠이 들었는지조차 모르겠어요
I'm not even sure he's asleep yet.
그럼 확인해 보지 그래?
Then why don't you find out?
할 수 없어요
I can't.
그한테서 자유로워지고 싶지 않아?
Don't you want to be free of him?
두려워요
I'm afraid.
난 아냐
Well, I'm not.
침실이 어디지?
Where's the bedroom?
베타 노드에 그룹 허가를 577로 설정해
Set the group permission
on the beta node to 577,
그리고 순환시켜서
트리 끝까지 가도록 해
and make it recursive,
all the way down the tree.
내가 다 할 때까지 사이퍼 볼륨에
있는 사람들은 작업을 멈춰
I want anyone who's on the cipher
volume to stay off until I'm done.
알았어요
Okay.
아담, 저 게이트웨이들은 열렸어?
Adam, are those gateways open?
그래, 물론이야
Yeah, of course.
바이러스 정의를 보내려고 해
I'm trying to seed a virus definition.
자료가 충분해야 할 텐데..
I hope you have enough to go on.
금방 알게 될 거야
We'll know in a minute.
너하고 킴이 등 뒤에서 날 배신한 걸
알고도 이걸 하고 있다니 슬픈 일이야
It's sad that I have to do this, knowing
that you and Kim stabbed me in the back.
내가 어떻게 했길 바라는 거야, 클로이?
What do you want me to do, Chloe?
넌 규칙을 어겼고, 그에 대해
모두에게 거짓말을 했지
You're breaking rules and then
lying about it all over the place.
너라면 어떻게 했겠어?
Tell me what you'd do.
난 내 동료에게 믿음을 더 가졌을 거야
I'd have more faith
in my fellow worker.
아니야, 절차를 지켰을 거야
No, you'd follow protocol.
넌 누구보다 규칙에 철저했지
You're the biggest
rule freak of anyone.
친구와 그 아기를 보호하기 위해서
I think I've done a pretty good job
at breaking the rules,
규칙을 참 잘 어긴 거 같아, 안 그래?
trying to protect a friend and
that baby, wouldn't you say?
어떤 친구?
What friend?
끝났어
It's done.
젠장!
Damn it!
성공하지 못했어
It didn't work.
웜이 더 빠르게 퍼지고 있어!
The worm's speeding up!
그게 어떻게 가능하지?
How is that possible?
뭔가를 작동시킨 게 틀림없어
We must have triggered something.
1번하고 4번을 열어
Open one and four.
그럼 커널이 노출되는 거 아냐?
Won't that expose the kernel?
그래, 하지만 선택의 여지가 없어
Yeah, but we have no choice.
어서 해!
Do it!
- 0-7?
- 아냐, 4-7
- No, 4-7.
그리고 마지막 건
지역번호가 206이야
Yes. And the last one on here
has a 206 area code.
- 워싱턴이요?
- 그래, 555-0191이야
- Washington?
- Yeah, that's 555-0191.
- 그게 다인가요?
- 그래
That's it? / Yeah.
- 알았어요
- 좋아
All right. / Okay.
아.. 그리고 브라이언트
Oh, and Bryant,
- 정말 고마워
- 괜찮아요?
- thank you so much.
- You okay?
그래, 나중에 전화해줘
Yeah, just call me.
그래
All right.
뭐 하는 거죠?
What are you doing?
알란이 이 전화로 한 통화들을
추적할 수 있는 사람이 있어
I have someone who can track the calls
that Alan made from this phone,
만약 그 중 하나라도
켈리하고 관련이 있다면
and if any of them can
be connected to Kelly,
우린 알란에게 불리한
증거가 있는 거야
we have evidence that
we can use against Alan.
- 난 뭘 할까요?
- 아무것도..
- What should I do?
- Nothing.
아무것도 할 필요 없어
그냥 자러 가
Absolutely nothing.
Just go to bed,
여기선 아무 일도 없었던 거야
and as far as you're concerned,
nothing happened here.
줄리아, 왜 자지 않는 거야?
Julia, why aren't you in bed?
누구하고 얘기하고 있어?
And who are you talking to?
셰리?
Sherry?
안녕, 알란
Hello, Alan.
줄리아, 당신한테 실망했어
Julia, I'm disappointed in you.
내가 오라고 한 게 아니에요
I didn't ask her here.
하지만 그녀를 들어오게 했지
But you let her in.
그리고 내 핸드폰도 가져갔어
And you took my cell phone as well.
아니
No,
내가 가져왔어요
I took the phone.
그래서 뭘 하려는 거야, 셰리?
So what do you think
you're going to do, Sherry?
날 막으려고?
Stop me?
그렇게는 안 될 거야
That's not likely.
알았어요
All right,
공개적으로 얘기하자는 거군요
좋아요
you want to talk
about this in the open? Fine.
케빈 켈리에게 무슨 일이 일어났죠?
What happened to Kevin Kelly?
케빈 켈리라..
Kevin Kelly--
그 이름 기억나는군
the name rings a bell.
오, 물론 그래야죠
well, it should ring a bell.
그는 당신이 12년 전에 그의 딸을
차로 쳐서 죽인 걸 본 사람이니까요
He's the man that saw you run over
his daughter and kill her 12 years ago.
입막음으로 상당한 돈을
주었던 사람이죠
The man you paid a considerable
amount of money to keep quiet.
그리고 오늘밤 당신이
사라지게 만든 사람이고요
And the man you made
disappear tonight.
그러니 그걸 좀 곰곰이
생각해 보지 그래요?
So why don't you
chew on that a bit?
어쩌면 내일 좀 더
얘기할 수 있겠군요
And maybe we can talk about it
a little more tomorrow.
아니면 지금 끝낼 수도 있죠
Or we can end it now,
당신이 데이비드한테서 떨어진다면..
and you can back off David.
- 네, 바우어입니다
- 클로이 오브라이언이 기다립니다
- Yeah, this is Bauer.
- Chloe O'Brian for you, sir.
좋아요, 연결해줘요
Fine. Patch her through.
니나, 당신에 대해 모두 들었어
Nina, I've heard all about you.
당신이 살기 위해 한 짓이 인상적이더군
I know what you've done, and how
you've managed to stay alive is impressive.
하지만 잭을 한 번 더
속이려고 한다면
But if you try to play
Jack one more time,
그는 당신을 죽일 거야
he's going to kill you.
그런가?
Is that so?
그래
Yeah.
스피커폰으로 해놓을게
I'm going to put you
on speakerphone.
3분 후면 우리 시스템
전체가 죽을 거야
In about three minutes, our entire
system's going to be down.
협상을 바란다면 이걸 어떻게 멈추는지
지금 말하는 게 좋을 거야
You want any leverage, you better start
telling me how to stop this thing now.
그렇게 빨리 움직이진 않아, 잭
It doesn't move that fast, Jack.
네가 틀렸어
클로이, 화면에 띄워봐
You're wrong.
Chloe, put it up on the screen.
협상할 시간이 점점 줄고 있어
You're running out of
time here to cut a deal.
그녀한테 설명해줘, 클로이
Explain it to her, Chloe.
동부 해안의 라우터들을 분리하려고 하자
웜의 속도가 세 배가 됐어요
When I try to separate the routers
in the east coast, the worm speed tripled.
누구지?
Who is this?
클로이 오브라이언이에요
Chloe O'Brian.
My network monitor's up.
네트워크 모니터를 띄웠어요
어떻게 하죠?
What do I do?
사용자 아이디 CIS27A로 접속을 해
Log in with user I.D. "CIS27A."
보안 등급을 요구해요
It's asking for a security level.
esc하고 6을 눌러
Hit escape six.
- 그게 다예요?
- 그래
That's it? / Yes.
클로이, 그게 멈췄나?
Chloe, did that stop it?
아니요
No.
잠깐만요
Wait a minute.
멈추진 않았지만 느려지고 있어요
It didn't stop it, but
it's slowing down.
시간이 얼마나 더 있지?
How much more time
do we have?
모의실험상으로는
겨우 20분 정도예요
Our simulation says
just over 20 minutes.
다시 전화할게
I'll get back to you.
좋아, 내가 느려지게 했어
Okay, so I slowed it down.
이제 비행기를 돌려서 멕시코로 가
Now you need to turn the plane
around and head back to Mexico.
그렇게 안 하면, 전 세계의 잠복요원들이
1시간 안에 죽기 시작할 거야
If you don't, you can expect your
undercover agents around the world
to start dying within the hour.
니나, 넌 LA로 돌아갈 거야
Nina, you're going back to Los Angeles.
넌 아마도어 찾는 걸 도울 거고
그런 다음 감옥으로 갈 거야
You're going to help me find Amador,
and then you're going to prison.
그게 앞으로 일어날 일이야
That's what's happening here.
당신 가족을 위해서 모든 걸
해줬는데 내 집에 찾아 왔군!
You come into my house after
everything I've done for your family?!
난 당신 아이들의 아버지를
미국 대통령으로 만들어 줬어!
I've made your children's father
the President of the united states!
잠깐만요
You wait a minute. Whatever you did to help
David was not for the benefit of my children.
당신이 데이비드를 돕기 위해 뭘 했든
우리 애들을 위해서 한 건 아니에요
똑바로 얘기해요
Let's get that straight.
가진 게 돈밖에 없어서 친구를 돈으로
지배하는 당신은 소인배예요, 알란
You're just a small man, Alan,
who lords his money over his friends
because that's all you have.
그게 바로 당신의 실체죠!
That's all you are!
왜 당신 아내가 밖에 나가
다른 남자를 찾았겠어요?
Why do you think your wife had to
go out and find another man?
- 이런 식으로 나한테 말하지 마!
- 당신은 그녀의 사랑이 아니니까요!
- Don't you talk to me like this!
- Because you're not one!
당신 돈이 아니라면 당신을 매력 있다고
생각할 여자는 없어요, 알란
Not one woman in her right mind
would find you attractive
without your wealth, Alan.
그게 사람들이 당신한테 원하는 거고
줄리아가 원하는 모두예요
That's what people want from you.
That's all Julia wants from you.
그런데 내가 당신을
두려워할 것 같은가요?
And I'm supposed
to be afraid of you?
당신을 무서워한다고 생각하나요?
You think I'm scared of you?
당신은 그냥 작은 소년이야, 알란
You're just a little boy, Alan,
불쌍하고 왜소하고 병약한 작은 소년!
a pathetic, scrawny,
sickly little boy!
줄리아, 내 약..
Julia, my pills.
내 약..
My pills.
아니, 안 돼
No, don't.
- 뭐 하는 거예요?
- 안 돼
What are you doing? / Don't.
셰리
Sherry. / Don't. / Julia!
- 안 돼
- 줄리아!
- 이게 당신이 빠져나갈 기회야
Julia! / This is your way out.
줄리아!
Julia!
좋아, 우린 여기 있어선 안 돼, 줄리아
All right, we can't stay here, Julia.
- 우리가 그를 죽였어요
- 아니, 아무도 그를 죽이지 않았어
- We killed him.
- No, no, no one killed him.
- 우린 그가 죽는 걸 지켜봤어요
- 아니야, 끝났어, 줄리아
- We watched him die.
- No, it's over, Julia.
- 그가 죽는 걸 지켜봤다고요!
- 끝났어! 쉿!
- We watched... him die!
- It's over!
자, 알란은 아픈 사람이었어
Now Alan was a sick little man.
그의 약한 몸의 기력이 다했고
주위에 도와줄 사람이 없었어
And his weak body gave out.
Nobody was around to help him.
그리고 당신은 침실에 있었어
And you, you were in your bedroom.
알아들어?
Understand me?
당신은 이제 자유야
You're free of him, sweetie.
그것만 생각하면 돼
That's all you need to think about.
하지만 경찰이 와서 물어 볼 때
But there's one thing you're gonna
have to be really clear about,
이거 하나는 분명히 해야 돼
when the authorities come
around questioning you:
이건 사고였어
This was an accident.
- 난 할 수 없을 것 같아요
- 당신은 선택의 여지가 없어
- I don't think I can do this.
- You don't have a choice.
앞으로 불쌍한 여생을
감옥에서 보내고 싶지 않다면..
Unless you want to spend the rest
of your pretty little life in prison.
오, 세상에
Oh, god.
좋아, 침실로 가
All right, you go into your bedroom.
거기서 한 시간 정도 있어
You stay there for about an hour.
그리고 물을 마시러 나와서
Then you're gonna come out
for a glass of water,
당신은..
and then you're gonna...
당신은 시체를 보게 되는 거야
you're gonna see the body.
그게 당신 이야기야
Now that's your story.
어디에 전화를 하죠?
Who do I call?
911.
그게 보통 하는 거잖아, 그렇지?
That's what you would
naturally do, right?
알았어요
당신은 어떻게 할 거죠?
Okay. What about you?
아니, 아니야, 들어봐
No, no, you listen.
이건 정말 중요하니까
주의 깊게 들어
You listen real strong
'cause this is very crucial.
만약 누군가..
If anyone...
내가 여기 있었다고 의심을 하면
suspects that I was here,
조사가 진행될 거고
there will be an investigation,
우리 둘 다 감옥에 가게 될 거야
and both of us will go to prison.
난 여기 없었어
I was never here.
알아들어?
You understand?
줄리아, 내가 한 말 알아들었다고
지금 당장 말해
Julia, you tell me right now that
you understand what I'm saying.
알아들었어요
I understand.
좋아
Okay.
젠장, 그 연산을 멈춰
Damn it.
Stop that process,
더 악화시키고 있어
it's making it worse.
- 클로이, 무슨 일이야?
- 아직 모르겠어요
- Chloe, what's going on?
- I'm not getting it.
- 어떻게 되는 거야?
- 모르겠어요
- What's it going to take?
- I don't know.
클로이, 네가 이 웜을 멈출 수 없다면
잭한테 니나가 원하는 곳으로
Chloe, if you can't stop this worm, then
I have to tell Jack to re-route that plane
비행기를 돌리라고 얘기해야 돼
to wherever Nina wants.
토니, 일 좀 하게 해줘요
Tony, please let me work.
- 바우어입니다
- 잭
It's Bauer. / Jack.
요원들이 이걸 처리하고
있다고 말해줘
Tell me your people have
got a handle on this thing.
우린 거의 다 도착했어
We're on final approach.
못 하고 있어요
We don't.
니나는 비행기를 멕시코로 돌릴 때까지
제거 암호를 주지 않을 거고
Nina's not gonna give us the kill code
until we turn the plane
around back to Mexico,
난 그럴 생각이 없어
and I have no intention of doing that.
우린 선택의 여지가 없어요
We don't have a choice.
조종사한테 지금
비행기를 돌리라고 해요
Tell the pilot to re-route the plane now.
이걸 막기 위해서는
뭐든지 해야 돼요
We have to do whatever it takes
to stop this thing.
토니, 그건 대안이 아냐..
Tony, that's not an alternative...
토니
Tony.
젠장
Son of a bitch.
일단 피해가 생기고 나면
넌 협상을 할 수 없을 거야
Once the damage is done,
you're not going to
be able to cut a deal.
지금 제거 암호를 말해
Give me the kill code now.
잭
Jack.
뭐야?
What?
생각해봐요
Think about it.
그녀가 원하는 걸
지금 당장 해줘야 돼요
You should give her
what she wants right now.
그건 별 가치가 없어요
It's not worth it.
그녀는 나중에 처리하면 되죠
We'll deal with her later.
잭, 만약 비행기를 돌리면
Jack, if you turn the plane around,
웜을 더 느리게 만들 수 있어
I can slow this thing down even more.
하지만 멕시코에서 안전할 때까지
제거 암호를 주지 않을 거야
But I'm not giving you the kill code
till I'm safe to Mexico.
무슨 일이지?
What's going on?
다시 올라가고 있어요
We're going back up.
개자식
Son of a bitch.
뭐 하는 거야?
What are you doing?
방금 알메이다 요원한테서
착륙하지 말라는 명령을 받았습니다
I just got orders from
Agent Almeida not to land.
그가 멕시코로 비행기를
돌리라고 했어요
He said to take the plane
back to Mexico.
지금 비행기를 착륙시켜
Land the plane now.
난 명령을 받았습니다
I got my orders.
꿈도 꾸지 마
Don't even think about it.
비행기를 착륙시켜
Land the plane.
뭐 하고 있는 거야?
What the hell is he doing?
중위, 무슨 일인가?
Lieutenant, what's going on?
왜 비행기를 돌리지 않는 거야?
Why aren't you turning
this plane around?
바우어가 못하게 합니다
Bauer won't let me.
그가 못하게 한다니 무슨 뜻이야?
What do you mean
he won't let you?
저한테 총을 겨누고 있습니다
He's got a gun on me.
스피커로 바꿔
Put me on speaker.
잭, 내 말 들려요?
Jack, can you hear me?
그래, 들려, 토니. 그리고 우린
이 비행기를 LA에 착륙시킬 거야
Yeah, I can hear you, Tony.
And we're landing this plane in Los Angeles.
그 제거 암호가 필요해요
We need that kill code.
조종사한테 지금 당장
비행기를 돌리라고 하세요
Tell the pilot to turn the plane
around right now.
본부로부터의 직접 명령이에요
That's an order straight from Division.
니나한테 계속 끌려 다닐 순 없어
We can't keep giving in to her.
잠깐만요
Wait a minute.
뭔가 얻은 것 같아요
I think I'm getting something.
그것에 희망을 걸 순 없어
I can't take that chance.
이걸 멈추지 않으면
많은 요원들이 죽을 거예요
We have to stop this thing,
or a lot of agents are
going to wind up dead.
그럼 우리 힘으로 멈춰야만 해
Then our people are
gonna have to stop it.
노력하고 있지만
시간이 없어요
We're trying.
We don't have the time.
비행기를 돌린다고
도움이 되는 건 아냐
Turning the plane around
is not going to help.
우리가 있어야 할 곳에서
점점 멀어질 뿐이야
It's just gonna take us farther
away from where we need to be.
- 클로이?
- 제발 입 다물어요, 토니
- Chloe...?
- Please shut up, Tony.
달튼, 50까지 다시 올려봐
Dalton, bring it back up to 50.
- 좋아
- 깨끗해
Okay.
I'm clear. / I'm clear.
What branches?
- 깨끗해
- 어떤 가지들이지?
- 14부터 20
- 넌 어때, 달튼?
- 14 through 20.
- What about you, Dalton?
그래, 작동하고 있어
라우터들이 돌아오고 있어
Yeah, it's working.
The routers are coming back up.
이제 괜찮은 건가?
Are we okay?
아직 몰라요
I can't tell.
그래, 여기, 여길 봐
다시 돌아오고 있어
Yeah, here, here,
it's coming back up.
안 돼, 멈춰!
연산을 멈춰!
No, stop!
Stop the process!
하지만 지금 돌고 있어, 클로이
거의 다 돌아왔어
But it's cycling through, Chloe.
It's almost back up.
그건 웜이 만든 방어체계야
It's a defense ploy built into the worm.
우리가 생각했던 게 아니었어
그냥 간단한 역전파 바이러스야
It's not what we thought,
it's a simple back-prop virus.
자원 포크를 빼내야겠어
I have to strip out the resource fork.
하지만 CPU를 봐
거의 100%야
But look at the CPU.
It's almost 100%.
젠장, 아담, 멈춰
모니터에 보이는 건 진짜가 아냐
Damn it, Adam, stop. What you're
seeing on the monitor isn't real.
그녀가 말한 대로 해
Do what she says.
좋아, 멈췄어
All right, it's stopped.
어떻게 된 거야?
What's going on?
스스로 리셋하는 것 같아요
I think it's resetting itself.
잡았어요
We got it.
- 잭?
- 그래
Jack? / Yeah.
- 다시 작동하고 있어요
- 완전 작동인가?
- We're back up.
- Fully functional?
완전 작동이에요
Fully functional.
우린 다시 착륙하겠어
We're resuming our approach.
잘했어
Good work.
당신 상관에게 보고를 해도 좋아
You can file a report with
your commanding officer.
우리 시스템 모두가
잘 돌아가고 있어
All our systems are
up and running.
당신 말 안 믿어
I don't believe you.
네가 뭘 믿든 상관없어
I don't care what you believe.
디렉터리에 손실된 것이
없는지 점검해 보자
Let's check our directories,
make sure we haven't lost anything.
알았어, 그렇게 할게
Yeah, I'm on it.
네트워크 클라이언트들은?
What about the network clients?
모두 켜질 때까지
한 번에 여섯 개씩 올리자
Let's remount those six at a time
until they're all on.
모두 좋아 보여
달튼, 그쪽은 어때?
Okay, these all look good.
Dalton, how about yours?
몇 가지 손실이 있지만
10분 안에 저절로 고쳐질 거야
There's some drop out, but it'll
self-adjust in the next ten minutes.
오늘 아주 잘했어, 클로이
Great work today, Chloe.
큰 손실이 될 뻔한 걸 막아 줬군
You averted what could
have been a major loss.
알아요
I know.
잭하고 체이스가 곧 돌아오나요?
Are Jack and Chase
coming back soon?
- 그래
- 좋아요
Yeah. / Good.
- 어디로 가는 거지?
- 다시 위층으로 가야죠
- Where are you going?
- Back upstairs.
아니야
No.
아기에 관한 일이
그냥 사라지진 않을 거야
This whole thing with the baby
isn't going to just go away.
오늘 세운 공로는 분명히 자네 사건에
좋게 반영될 테지만, 혐의는 아직 있어
What you did here will certainly bear well
on your case, but the charges still stand.
자넬 LA 경찰에 넘길 건데
무슨 일이 생기든
We're handing you over to LAPD,
and no matter what happens,
이 아이가 누구 아이인지
말해야 할 거야
you're going to have to tell them
who this baby belongs to.
저게 누구죠?
안젤라를 어디로 데려가요?
Who's that?
Where are they taking Angela?
그 애는 이제 아동보호소 관할이야
Child Protective Services
has custody of her now.
- 안 돼요, 그럴 수는 없어요
- 물론 그렇게 할 수 있어
- Oh, no, they can't do that.
- Of course they can.
아동보호관님, 잠깐만요!
Child Services!
Hold on.
클로이, 뭐 하는 거야?
Chloe, what are you doing?
누가 아버지인지 말하겠어요
I'll tell you who the father is.
어머니가 누군진 묻지 마세요
나도 몰라요
Don't ask me who the mother is,
I don't know.
난 호의를 베푼 거예요
I was doing a favor.
진실을 말한다고 맹세해요
I swear I'm telling the truth.
바브
Barb,
그 애를 좀 더 데리고 있어야겠네
we're going to hold
onto her a little longer.
방금 정보를 더 얻었어
We just got some more information.
왜 진작에 말하지 않았지?
Why didn't you tell me this earlier?
그가 누구한테도 말하지 말랬거든요
He didn't want me to tell anyone.
친구의 도리를 지켰을 뿐이에요
I was trying to be a friend.
미안해요
Sorry.
클로이
Chloe,
당신이 바이러스를
멈췄다고 들었어요
I heard you stopped the worm.
그래, 내가 했어
Yeah, I did.
네 아버지와 체이스가
LA로 돌아와서 안심이 되겠네
Your dad and Chase are back in L.A.
You must be relieved.
그래요. 고마워요
Yes. Thank you.
이봐요, 클로이
아기는 어떡해요?
Look, Chloe,
what about the baby?
그 애가 뭐?
What about her?
그들이 책임을 물을 거라고
생각했는데요
Well, I thought they were
pressing charges.
아니, 그건 오해였어
No. That was a misunderstanding.
클로이, 기다려요
Chloe, wait.
왜?
What?
그럼 그들이 책임을
묻지 않을 건가요?
So they're not pressing charges?
- 응
- 왜요?
No. / Why not?
어.. 애 아버지가 누군지 말했어
Uh, I told them who the father was,
- 그러니 모든 게 괜찮아
- 기다려요, 모든 게 괜찮다고요?
- and everything's okay.
- Wait, everything's okay?
왜요, 애 아버지가 누구죠?
Why, who's the father?
체이스야
Chase.
번역수정
김혜정(heather81@nate.com)
최종수정
오흥민(echem@nate.com)
동호회 외 무단유출을 금지합니다
(http://club.nate.com/24)
동호회외 무단유출을 금지합니다